紙牌屋
前情提要
翻譯   章魚埃克斯
時間軸   壬虛浪影
后期   餓得慌
校對  草草
顧問  老杜
總監  草草
紙牌屋
第六季  第六集
原創翻譯  雙語字幕
最新連載海外影視劇下載
請登陸 www.YYeTs.com
僅供交流學習  禁止商用盈利
阿卡斯公司
總統懷胎16周時墮胎
厄舍與俄國  關系有多深
第25修正案
25th Amendment.
她只要能力不足就行
She only needs to be deficient.
內閣聽命于你
The Cabinet is yours.
辭職
Resign.
其中有一封郵件是比爾·謝潑德的辦公室發的
There's an e-mail from Bill Shepherd's office in the chain.
他們早就知道會出人命
They knew somebody was gonna die.
這不是瑞秋·波斯納
That's not Rachel Posner.
她死了嗎
Is she dead?
我剛從新墨西哥州回來
I just got back from New Mexico.
你把瑞秋怎么了
What did you do with Rachel?
她在沙特阿拉伯的某個地方
She's somewhere in Saudi Arabia.
但必須有行政命令才能執行
But nothing can happen without an executive order.
那...
Well, then.
等你當了總統  再發布行政命令好了
That's gonna have to happen when you're president.
是俄羅斯人殺了湯姆
The Russians killed Tom...
馬克·厄舍幫忙掩蓋了事實
and Mark Usher covered it up.
我要你告訴聯調局
I need you to tell the FBI
你和湯姆的關系
about your relationship with Tom.
你們都被解雇了
You're all fired.
問問安奈特
Ask Annette--
問問你媽媽
Ask your mother.
她讓我問你我從哪來的
She told me to ask you where I came from.
見過我的新內閣
Meet my new cabinet.
我就想看看你的表情
I just wanted to see your face.
你扣下的遺囑在哪  你放哪了
The will you intercepted? Where is it?
已經不在我這兒了
I don't have it anymore.
他把一切都留給了你
He left you everything.
遺囑的結語就是這樣的
That's how the will ends.
"記住我最后給你的那樣東西"
"Remember the last thing I gave you."
弗蘭西斯死在這間屋子里
Francis died in this room.
殺了他的人
Whoever killed him
將得到她或他應有的下場
will get what she or he deserves.
湯姆
Tom.
湯姆  你在嗎
Tom, you here?
湯姆
Tom!
知情人士稱聯調局已經掌握了相關證據
Sources say that the FBI was made aware of the evidence
證實副總統及多名內閣成員
linking the vice president and a number of cabinet secretaries
與俄羅斯政府高層有聯系
with several senior Russian government officials.
與此同時  安德伍德總統
Meanwhile, President Underwood,
盡管仍未對此事發表任何評論
who has still not commented on the matter,
卻也有所動作  可能是為了撇清自己
in what could be construed as an attempt to distance herself
以及本屆政府與通俄事件的關系
and her administration from the apparent collusion,
她解除了所有遭指控閣員的職務
has fired all the accused cabinet secretaries,
為組建有史以來第一個
making way for the first-ever
全女性內閣鋪平了道路
all-female cabinet in US history.
不是一次  不是兩次
Not one, not two,
而是三次墮胎
but three abortions.
第三次胎兒已經16周了
The third one at 16 weeks.
想想吧
Think about it.
那已經不是幾個細胞
That's not a few cells
或一團組織那么大了
or a collection of cells.
差不多已經有四英寸半大小
It's more like four and a half inches long
3.5盎司[約100克]那么重了
and three and a half ounces.
16周的時候
At 16 weeks,
總統的胎兒應該已經有
the President's baby would have been the size...
這么大了
of this.
美國同胞們  當前有一些人
My fellow Americans, there are certain parties out there
希望利用我的個人生活攫取政治利益
that hope to use my private life for political gain.
下面的話  我只說一次
I'm going to say this exactly once.
多年來我和我已故的丈夫一直在嘗試組建家庭
For many years, my late husband and I tried to start a family.
我從前之所以不怎么提這事  是因為
I downplayed that fact in the past because...
這是一個痛苦的話題
Well, it's a painful subject.
當我終于懷孕的時候
When I finally became pregnant,
孩子卻發育不良
the baby wasn't viable,
所以不得不終止妊娠
and the pregnancy had to be terminated.
僅此而已
End of story.
孩子是健康孩子
The baby was viable.
但我和弗蘭西斯  不是好父母
Francis and I, as parents, were not.
我要說清楚
So, let me be clear.
這將是我最后一次談及這個話題
This is the last I will ever say on this subject.
好了
Okay.
今天在座的各位  都讓我非常驕傲
I am so proud of every person around this table.
她們每一個人都服務國家多年
Each of them has served this country
兢兢業業  忠于職守
with honor and distinction.
有些已經位列副部
Some as deputy secretaries.
她們都是美國人中的佼佼者
They are all accomplished Americans
在各自部門和領域中成就卓著
and members of their respective departments.
不過還是由她們介紹自己吧
But I'll let them speak for themselves.
大家好  我是珍妮佛·邦加頓
Hello, my name is Jennifer Baumgarten,
擔任代理聯邦檢察官
and I am the acting Attorney General of the United States.
珍妮會幫我大忙的
Jenny's going to come in very handy.
就司法部而言
And as far as the Justice Department is concerned,
我也認同總統清理門戶的努力
I share the President's commitment to cleaning house.
可是副總統出席所有內閣會議
But isn't it customary for the vice president
不是慣例嗎
to attend all cabinet meetings?
并不是必須出席
Not necessarily, no.
是這樣  自從我加入安德伍德政府
Listen, ever since I joined the Underwood administration,
總統和我始終合作緊密  信任無間
the President and I have worked together on a daily basis.
配合默契  我們就是這樣
Hand in glove. That's the way we work.
你被要求辭職是真的嗎
Is it true that you were asked to resign?
什么  當然沒有
What? No.
沒有
No.
至于我通俄的指控  更是荒唐
And the Russians and me, it's preposterous.
我和總統都同意
Look, the President and I agree
揪出這些不實指控背后主謀的最好辦法
the best way to find out who's behind these accusations
就是任命一位特別檢察官
is to appoint a special prosecutor.
讓他或她依法履職
And let him or her do her job.
-非常感謝  -再問一個問題  一個問題
- Thanks very much. - One more question, one question!
副總統先生  再問一個問題
Mr. Vice President, one question.
再問一個
One more question!
副總統先生
Mr. Vice President!
副總統先生  再問一個  再問一個
Mr. Vice President, one question, one more question!
好的  好的  謝謝你  很好
Okay. Great. Thank you. Great.
好的  謝謝  謝謝你  再見
Okay, good. Thanks, thanks. Bye.
她找到它了嗎
Did she find him?
湯姆
Tom.
-她找到它了嗎  -沒有
- Did she find him? - No.
前門開著
Front door was open.
狗不見了  屋里也沒人
Dog's not there. No one was there.
湯姆  我太抱歉了  我感覺沒別的辦法了
Okay, Tom, I am so sorry. I felt like I had no other option.
我發誓
I mean, I swear,
-我真的看見你房子里有人  -我知道
- I saw someone inside your... - No, I know. I know.
要不我們再回去找找  可是
We can go circle back and take another look if you want, but...
這不是個好主意
That doesn't sound like a good idea.
你的傳真
That's your fax.
很好
Great.
多少錢
How much is that?
首張一塊九  續張每張一塊二毛五
$1.90 for the first page, $1.25 for each additional.
看起來你續張可不少呢
And it looks like you've got quite a few additionals coming in.
我能不能...
But can I just...
讓我算算一共要花多少錢
Let me just figure out how much it's gonna cost.
這些錢足夠了
That's more than enough.
是啊  謝謝你
Yeah, thank you.
給你
Here you go.
-謝謝  -客氣
- Thank you. - You bet.
39.3度
102.7.
你干嗎讓護士走
Why did you send the nurse away?
因為她也得吃飯
Because she needed to eat.
而且我感覺還行
And I feel fine.
-我看你還行才怪  -不不  你看
- I find this anything but fine. - No, no, look...
發燒是好事
This fever's good.
但我覺得不該燒這么久
I don't think it's supposed to last this long.
要我給你換床單嗎
Do you want me to change the sheets?
反正還會濕的
What's the point?
你知道我無論如何都支持你
You know, I support you no matter what.
不管你想嘗試什么療法
Whatever you want to try,
但是這也...
but this is...
研究成果很樂觀
Research is very good.
在歐洲也臨床驗證過了
Proven effective in Europe.
你還記得
Do you remember
老爸總是逼我穿長袖吃晚餐嗎
how dad used to make me wear long sleeves at dinner?
你想他們嗎
Do you miss them?
想媽  不想他
Her, not him.
他總是對是非對錯那么篤定
He was always so sure about what was right.
媽媽的疑慮經年累月  反倒讓她更深刻了
Mom's doubt actually allowed her to deepen as time went by.
深刻也沒那么好
Depth is overrated.
明天要不要取消
Do you want to cancel tomorrow?
怎么能取消呢
We can't cancel.
怎么了  安妮
What's wrong, Annie?
安妮
Annie?
我一直打鄧肯的電話
I keep calling Duncan.
他不回話  也不回家
And I've heard nothing, and he still hasn't gone home.
你知道他早晚會發現的
You knew he was gonna find out someday.
也許這樣最好
Maybe it's for the best.
如果您餓了渴了
If you're hungry or thirsty...
我生氣  累  還難過
Angry. Tired. Frustrated.
我現在應該接受詢問了
I should've been debriefed by now.
如果您需要水或者咖啡的話
Again, if you need water or a cup of coffee...
這太荒唐了
This is ridiculous.
失陪下
Excuse me.
沒有可見的傷痕
No visible scars.
看來你已經看過醫生了
I assume you've been looked at by a physician.
這是程序
It's protocol.
和局里高層聯絡也是
So is talking with a senior member of the Agency.
今天你是見不著他們了
That won't be happening today.
你基本上  廢了
You're essentially burnt
不管是你和哪個情報局的工作
when it comes to your work with any of the agencies.
是這么說的吧  "廢了"
That's the term, isn't it, burnt?
不非得這么說
Not necessarily.
差不多都這么說
Virtually always.
沒人知道你被監禁期間說了什么  沒說什么
Nobody knows what you said or didn't say while in captivity.
我沒說  克萊爾
I didn't say, Claire.
是總統女士
Madam President.
你聽說馬克的事了嗎
Oh, and have you heard about Mark?
他把自己變成了一出好戲
He's made quite a spectacle of himself.
也許過不了多久  我就不得不發話了
I don't know how much longer I can keep my voice out of it.
我猜他是以為他可以全身而退
I guess he thought he could come out from under it.
是啊  那些最了解我們的人
Yes. Well, the people that know us best,
也最知道怎么傷害我們
know best how to hurt us.
安德伍德總統
President Underwood...
其實我已經改回娘家姓黑爾了
Actually, I've gone back to "Hale."
你錯了  如果你認為我參與了...
You're wrong if you think I have...
你不告訴我實情  就太傻了
You are foolish if you don't tell me what it is.
猜猜我不想再忍受哪種人了  簡
Guess which kind of people I'm done suffering, Jane.
你是來對了
You were wise to come.
我告訴過你了  我也會告訴他們
I told you and I'll tell them.
我不想要這份工作
I don't want the job.
道格  你決定前  務必聽他們說完
Doug, just promise you'll hear them out before you do anything.
而且提醒你一句  比爾現在不跟人握手
And just so you're aware, Bill's not shaking hands at the moment.
道格  給你介紹一下
Doug. May I introduce you?
安奈特和比爾·謝潑德
Annette and Bill Shepherd.
你好
Hello.
你還認得弗萊德·安博格吧
You remember Fred Amburg.
道格  說真的
Doug, for the record,
我很喜歡在療養院和你聊天
I really enjoyed our conversations in the facility.
行了
Come on, man.
條條大路通羅馬
All roads lead to Rome, you know?
安奈特和比爾就是羅馬
And Annette and Bill are Rome.
來請坐吧  斯坦普先生
Come. Sit down, please, Mr. Stamper.
他們正要走
These guys were just leaving.
再會了  謝潑德先生
Well, Mr. Shepherd,
-安奈特  -布雷特
- Annette. - Brett.
回頭再聊  比爾
Talk soon, Bill.
-弗萊德  -安奈特
- Fred. - Annette.
弗蘭克對你評價很高  道格
Frank spoke very highly of you, Doug.
你冷嗎  我可以讓他們把空調關了
You cold? I can have 'em switch off the AC.
這地方太潮了  我的天啊
Humidity in this town, my God,
感覺就像
makes you feel like
住在狗嘴巴里似的  是不是
you're living inside the mouth of a dog, doesn't it?
弗萊德里克·古斯塔夫·安博格
Frederic Gustav Amburg
是我最好的朋友
is my very best friend
認識52年了
over 52 years.
我們換過玻璃球
We've traded marbles,
交易過股票
stocks...
有一次還換過未婚妻
a fiancée once upon a time.
請坐吧  你站在那我都緊張了
Please. You're making me nervous standing there.
老天  別糾結個沒完了
Oh, Jesus Christ. Get over it.
你應該覺得自己命好
You should consider yourself lucky
還有弗萊德在那兒陪你
you had Fred to talk to in there.
你就像是那種找到99.9萬美元卻說
You're like the guy who finds $999,000 and says
"怎么不是100萬呢"的人
"Yeah, but it isn't a million."
布雷特·科爾將成為議長
Brett Cole will be the speaker.
如果不算馬克  他就是下一個總統繼任者
Next in line, if you don't count Mark.
我們得把那女人趕下臺
We've gotta get this woman outta there!
斯坦普先生  只要說到關于總統的話題
Mr. Stamper, my brother gets a little impatient
我哥哥就會比較急躁
when it comes to the President.
我們知道她是我們的共同敵人
We know we share a common enemy in her.
他留給你的東西肯定很有破壞力
Whatever he left you must be damning.
這我們還是知道的
We know that much.
弗蘭克知道  除了他就只有你
Frank knew you were the only other man
知道他妻子有多大的本事
who truly knew what his wife was capable of.
你是他唯一相信
The only one he could trust
能在時機到來時做正確的事的人
to do the right thing when the time came.
除非弗蘭克看錯了你
Unless, Frank was wrong about you.
一把拆信刀
A letter opener.
那是什么意思
What does that mean?
你們怎么看到遺囑的
How did you get your hands on the will?
這就叫人脈
It's called reach.
問題在于
You see, the thing is,
把她拉下臺的東西
whatever brings her down,
也會毀掉弗蘭西斯
could bring Francis down, as well.
你給我聽著
Now you listen to me.
弗蘭克是個能人
Frank was a hell of a guy.
我們本來要一起成就一番事業
We were going to accomplish great things together.
但此事關乎國家未來  太過重大
But this is too damn important for the future of this country.
一個包括你的未來
A future that includes you.
過去的就讓他過去吧
The past is just that.
等等
Hold on a second.
你是給妹妹還是哥哥干活
Do you work for the brother or the sister?
給他們家族
The family.
她不怎么喜歡你
She's not that fond of you.
我想讓你知道的
I wanted you to know.
什么  我其實一直在為他們效力嗎
What? That I was working for them all along?
不管怎么說  是弗蘭西斯給了我們這工作
One way or another, Francis got both of us hired.
我們也知道你和湯姆·哈默施密特的見面
We know you've been meeting with Tom Hammerschmidt.
你最近最好還是離他遠點
You need to stay away from him for a while.
天啊  這電梯怎么這么慢
God, this thing takes forever.
我什么都沒做錯
I have done nothing wrong.
我告訴你  我要揭露她
And I'll tell you something, I am going to expose her.
那自己也會受牽連
And yourself.
那時你該怎么辦
And then where will you be?
-你腦子不清楚了  馬克  -你這是怎么了
- You're not thinking, Mark. - What happened?
她拿住你了嗎
Did she get to you?
你被她要挾住了  是這樣嗎
She got to you, is that what you're saying?
我只是說她那雙藍眼睛里的神色變了
I'm saying something's changed in those steely blue eyes of hers.
抽身吧
Walk away.
我強烈建議你立即從這一團亂中抽身
My recommendation is walk away from this shit show.
不  我不能走
No. I'm not doing that.
你當初都不想要這個職位
You never even wanted this.
如今卻要為了它戰斗至死嗎
And now you're willing to fight to the death for it?
誰說要"至死"了
Who said anything about "the death?"
去她的  簡
Fuck her, Jane.
操
Fuck!
去她的
Fuck her.
請原諒
Forgive me,
但你為什么總是看不準時機
but why is your timing always off?
我還想幫你脫身
I tried to get you out.
脫身
Out.
多么奇怪的概念啊
What a quaint concept.
想要脫身  當初就不應該卷進來
When the only way out was never to get in in the first place.
我發過誓  我發過誓的
I swore. I swore.
我曾發誓永遠不會再進這座房子了
I swore I would never set foot in this house again.
你為什么要來這里
What the hell are you doing here?
局面已經很糟了  馬克
The optics are awful, Mark.
真的很糟
I mean, really.
只有在這里  我才覺得安心
It's the only place I feel safe.
風景很美  她選那里我也能理解
That looks lovely. I don't blame her for choosing it.
那種偏綠的藍色
And that blue-green color,
一看就是法國阿爾卑斯山的顏色
it's so specific to the French Alps.
天藍色  沒錯  天藍色
Azure, yes, azure.
當然了  咱們的關稅協議
Well, of course our little tariff agreement
確實引起了一些恐慌  維克多
caused some consternation, Viktor,
但我并不后悔  你也不后悔吧
but I don't regret it. Tell me you don't, either.
現在嗎
Right now?
也沒在干什么
Nothing, really.
就是籌劃未來
Just planning for the future.
舊的不去...
Out with the old.
是
Yeah.
三天前誰他媽知道珍妮佛·邦加頓是哪號人物
And exactly who the fuck was Jennifer Baumgarten 72 hours ago?
因為我要你爭取特別檢察官
Because I want you to push for a special prosecutor.
或者  那聽證會也行
Or... Well, hearings then.
因為你要是敢...
Because it will if you...
米切  少糊弄我
Mitch, don't give me that.
你敢做就能行
It will if you do.
因為我在共和黨的年資
Because I was a Republican a lot longer
可比在民主黨長多了  你知道
than I was a Democrat. You know it.
-聽著  米切  -再考慮到剛曝光的
- Listen to me, Mitch... - Considering the latest revelations
副總統的新案情  任誰也不能否認了
regarding the vice president, there's no denying it.
這些指控非常嚴重  決不能應付了事
These are serious allegations that cannot be ignored.
而我有種感覺  這只是冰山一角而已
And something tells me this is just the tip of the iceberg.
他們的關系到底有多深
I mean, how deep does this go?
-什么  我回頭打給你  -又有什么企圖
- What? I'll call you back. - And to what end?
-我們有權知道  -因為我得回頭打給你
- We deserve to know. Look... - 'Cause I need to call you back.
人們一直想給我貼一個政黨立場
People want to associate me with one party or another.
但在價值觀  生活方式上
I'm simply an American when it comes to values,
我只是個普通美國人
way of life.
斯圖爾特小姐和湯姆·耶茨
You have Ms. Stewart meeting with Tom Yates
在副總統家里幽會
in the vice president's home.
而這個湯姆·耶茨  如今也被爆出
Tom Yates, who we now know
是俄羅斯非常感興趣的人
was someone the Russians were very interested in.
而現在  這個副總統
And now you have the vice president
又縮在他的安全屋里
holed up in that safe house,
向我們保證一切都...
assuring us that everything is...
所有媒體都在要求評論
Every news outlet is asking for comment.
哪怕你不是天才  也能想明白
It doesn't take a genius to realize...
有的人就是想看別人跌跟頭  太可鄙了
It's terrible how people live to see others fail.
我已經很難繼續在白宮擔任任何職務了
It's going to be hard for me to continue here in any capacity.
正相反  凱爾茜
On the contrary, Kelsey,
我要任命你為我的正式新聞發言人
I am naming you my permanent press secretary.
-女士  我不...  -下次我見記者時
- Ma'am, I ca... I... - I'm going to announce it
就會宣布任命
the next time I take questions.
至于現在這段時間
For the time being, though,
我想還是由我親自來開例行新聞發布會吧
I think I should handle the daily press briefings.
我想我也該多露露面了
I feel like I need to give them a little face time.
您不明白  我不能...
You don't understand, I can't...
需要你開口的時候  我會告訴你
I will let you know when you need to speak.
別擔心  我們一起挺過去
Don't worry. We'll get through this together.
我今天在衣柜里看見了這個
Listen, I saw this in my closet today.
我就想到了你
And I thought of you.
我希望你收著
I want you to have it.
湯姆本來想搬回紐約
Tom was looking to move back to New York.
我們可以喝喝咖啡  偶爾共進晚餐
We would have coffee, the occasional dinner.
他告訴我他認識了一個人
He told me he was involved with somebody
讓他深陷其中
he couldn't get away from.
這讓他煎熬至極
That it was killing him.
真讓人不忍去想
I can't think about it.
我也不會去想
I won't think about it.
凱爾茜該怎么處理呢
What to do about Kelsey?
你瞧瞧那張臉
I mean, look at that face.
希望你喜歡那包
Enjoy the bag.
梅樂蒂·科魯茲的評論節目
So what Melody Cruz just said on the air,
我猜是你兒子搞的鬼吧
that was your son, I'm guessing.
你得和他談談  不然我去找他
You need to talk to him or I will.
-你小點聲  比爾在休息  -鄧肯在哪
- Keep your voice down. Bill's resting. - Where is Duncan?
-不在這  -比爾  比爾·謝潑德
- Not here. - Bill. Bill Shepard.
他今天不會見你的
Won't be seeing you today.
你還擦這個呢
Still wearing it?
你為什么由著他們搞臭我
Why are you allowing me to be gutted?
-搞臭  -沒錯  搞臭
- Gutted? - Yes, gutted.
搞臭  搞臭
Gutted, gutted.
是我讓梅樂蒂·科魯茲發的評論
I told Melody Cruz to run the piece.
我一直對你忠心耿耿
I have been nothing but loyal to you.
新聞發言人去了你家
The press secretary was in your house
-和湯姆·耶茨偷情  -天啊  得了吧
- with Tom Yates. - Oh, my God. Come on.
哪怕這里面毫無事實可言
Even if there isn't an ounce of truth to it.
馬克  這出通俄丑聞核心就是你
Mark, you're the face of this whole Russia fiasco.
這對國家不利
It's bad for the country.
對比爾和我也沒好處
It's bad for Bill and me.
你需要盡快處理掉
You need to get rid of it.
需要的話把房子燒了也行
Burn your house down, if you have to.
處理掉一切你和丑聞有關的證據
Anything that connects you to the story
然后控制一下情緒
and get a hold of yourself.
局里對關于馬克·厄舍案的最新線索
How's the Bureau feeling about the latest revelations
有什么看法
when it comes to Mark Usher?
不容易查  因為所有證據
It's difficult when all the evidence
都是從俄情報部門來的
is coming from Russian intelligence.
但我們必須得追查所有線索
But we have to follow every lead.
說實話  女士
To be honest, ma'am,
副總統在首都圈里人緣很好
the vice president is well-liked around town.
是  但這畢竟是嚴重罪行  納森
Yes, but we're talking about very serious crimes here, Nathan.
是  女士
Yes, ma'am.
告訴我  道格知道你在監聽后
So, tell me, once Doug knew you were listening in...
他最近基本都在公開行動
He's been operating pretty much in plain sight.
他還想和湯姆·哈默施密特見面
He tried to meet with Tom Hammerschmidt.
又要見
Again?
他去海亞當斯酒店見了比爾和安奈特·謝潑德
And he met with Bill and Annette Shepherd at the Hay-Adams.
此外他回住所時還帶了一條狗
Also, he returned to his apartment with a canine.
道格養了條狗
Doug has a dog?
他的公寓里有一只
There's one in his apartment.
另外我還注意到一件事
Another thing that caught my attention
就是我們派去監視
was the two men we have following
治療道格的心理醫生的兩個人聯系了我
Doug's psychiatrist from the facility contacted me.
說羅森醫生似乎被嚇壞了
Seems Dr. Rosen was pretty shaken up.
他說他摔倒在地  還昏過去了
He said he blacked out and fell down.
但我覺得根本說不通
But I mean, it doesn't make any sense...
-你太心不在焉了  納森  -什么
- You sound very distracted, Nathan. - Excuse me?
我不知道是因為你得起夜照顧孩子
I don't know if it's the lack of sleep
導致的睡眠不足
because of the night feedings,
但我不禁在想  你還能不能做好
but I wonder if you're still capable of doing the job
我交給你的工作
that I expect of you.
我向您保證  女士
I promise you, ma'am,
我完全能夠履行職務
I'm fully capable of executing my duties.
男孩還是女孩
Boy or girl?
-男孩  -我真為你們高興  納森
- A boy. - I'm so happy for you, Nathan.
俗話都說二婚最幸福
They do say second marriages are the best.
幾點了
What time is it?
別管時間了
Don't worry about it.
你還好嗎
Are you okay?
我給你量量體溫吧
Can I check your temperature?
不要
No.
每次我一醒過來
Every time I wake up,
你們就對我摸來戳去的
you people put your hands all over me.
我上床的時候53歲
When I went to bed, I was 53 years old.
現在都不知道自己多老了
I don't know how old I am.
馬克來過了嗎
Was Mark here?
我聽見他聲音了  我一直迷迷糊糊的
I heard these voices, I was going in and out.
-賽斯  -比爾
- Seth! - Bill,
-你還是回房間吧  -不  我還沒死
- maybe you should go back to your room. - No, I'm not dead yet.
他來過了嗎
Was he here?
-來過  但是  -斯克斯基女士找到了嗎
- Yes, but... - Okay. Well, where is Ms. Skorsky?
我們派了人在找了
We have people looking for her.
我們能確定她還在華盛頓
We're fairly sure she's still in the DC area.
但她手里有什么
But what does she have?
我們知道雷·麥耶斯
We now know that Ray Meyers
向這里的一家打印店
was faxing some kind of document
傳真了一些文件
to a copy shop here in the city.
那個道格·斯坦普有什么回信嗎
And anything from your Doug Stamper?
還沒  先生
No, sir.
比爾  求你了  你還在發燒
Bill, please, you're still feverish.
你能稍等下嗎
Can you give us a minute?
當然
Of course.
它在哪
Where is he?
它很安全
He's safe.
你可就未必了
Which is more than I can say for you.
知道嗎  有時候我都分不清你是在威脅我
You know, at times I can't tell if you're making a threat
還是想幫忙
or offering help.
賽斯·格雷森為什么要找簡寧·斯克斯基
Why is Seth Grayson looking for Janine Skorsky?
我想那些
I'm assuming the men
把你家翻得底朝天的人想找的就是她
who turned your place upside down were looking for her.
她在寫一篇報道
She's working on an article.
但她必須得另找一家報紙發表
But she'll have to find someplace else to publish.
她所在的報社被謝潑德家買下了
Her newspaper was bought by the Shepherds.
我們需要再見一面  湯姆
We still need to meet, Tom.
是
Yeah.
還有  道格
And, Doug,
你要是敢傷那小家伙一根毛
you lay a hand on that innocent animal,
我對天發誓  我把你腸子打出來
and I swear to Christ, I'll beat the living shit out of you.
你的狗沒事
Your dog's fine.
賽斯
Seth?
我知道你很尊敬我哥哥
I know you look up to my brother.
而且你也很周到
And you've been very attentive.
但他身體不太好
But he's not well, okay?
所以從此刻起
And from this moment on,
任何你認為需要向他匯報的消息
any information you think he needs,
都要先經過我
I need to hear it first.
我明白
I understand.
他會恢復的
He will recover.
謝謝你這么說
Thank you for saying that.
道格·斯坦普不喜歡被人呼來喝去
Doug Stamper doesn't like to be told what to do.
只有讓他覺得是他自己的點子才行
It only works if he thinks it's his idea.
話說
Listen,
也許不關我事
it may be none of my business,
但自從鄧肯收到了一個白宮寄來的包裹
but I haven't been able to reach Duncan
我就再也聯系不到他了
since he received a package from the White House.
我不知道包裹里是什么
I don't know what it was.
但他非常難過
But he was very upset.
謝謝
Thank you.
你說得對
You're right.
確實不關你事
That's none of your business.
我極力說服他  相信我
I urged him. Believe me.
我勸他自己辭職
I urged him to resign,
但他至多也就一半時間聽我的
but he listens to me half the time, at best.
我需要你理解
I need you to understand.
我不想再傷害馬克了
I don't want to hurt Mark again.
曾經有個迷茫的年輕女孩
There was a troubled young woman...
為什么好多故事的開頭都是這句話呢
I wonder why so many stories have to begin that way.
我知道  我也不喜歡這個故事
I know. I know. I hate this story.
我也不想告訴你
I hate that I'm telling you.
犧牲品女孩的故事我也講膩了
I'm tired of the disposable girl story.
布雷特·科爾第一次競選時她來做志工
She started as a volunteer on Brett Cole's first campaign.
馬克和我是顧問
Mark and I were consulting.
布雷特的妻子那時都快臨盆了
Brett's wife was as pregnant as could be.
而這個迷茫的姑娘卻非要纏著他不放
And the troubled young woman wouldn't leave him alone.
至少布雷特是這么說的
Well, that's how Brett characterized it.
他有沒有試圖吸引她
Did he encourage her attention?
享受她的迷戀
Enjoy it?
那是自然的
You bet he did.
他是個男人  有男人的自大
He's a man with a man's ego.
總之最后出了大亂子
Anyway, of course it became a mess
就像這類故事一慣的那樣
in all the ways these stories do.
于是收拾局面就成了馬克的任務
And suddenly, it was Mark's job to clean it up.
他逼她逼得太緊
He leaned on her too hard.
糾纏她  羞辱她
Badgered and berated her.
"你要毀了布雷特的未來
"You're ruining Brett's future.
你就該消失"
You better disappear."
于是她就消失了
And so she did.
她從羅斯福大橋上跳下去了
She jumped off the Roosevelt Bridge.
這事把馬克徹底嚇壞了  克萊爾
It fucked with Mark's head, Claire.
從此他就嚇破了膽  他
He lost his nerve after that. He...
他開始對一切都充滿懷疑
He started to question everything.
一切
Everything.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我不該這樣的
I'm... I mean, this is not me.
簡
Jane.
你知道你是在救他吧
You're saving him, you know that, right?
實話告訴我吧
Now, tell me the truth.
是你幫助凱茜逃跑的嗎
Did you help Cathy get away?
俄羅斯聯邦安全局可幫了大忙
The FSB have been very helpful, so you know.
他們很快就要找到凱茜了
They're very close to locating Cathy.
我注意到你每次要撒謊的時候
I've noticed that you always adjust your hair
總會撩一撩頭發
right before you tell a lie.
我想告訴你  我原諒你了
I want you to know I forgive you.
她想彈劾我
She wants to try and impeach me?
好啊  來啊  我等著呢
Be my guest, I cannot wait.
他們恨她  跟你說
They hate her, you know.
眾議院  所有參議員  恨死她了
The House, all the Senators, they hate her guts.
等到事情結束  她就會求我...
By the time this thing is over, she'll be begging me to...
別這么做
Don't do this.
我為了這個沒良心的女人做了這么多...
Everything I've done for that ungrateful...
別讓這種事再次發生
Don't let this happen again.
我沒能照顧好你
I didn't take proper care of you.
作為朋友
As a friend.
文藝復興時期意大利政治家  外交官
馬基雅維利終生流放
Machiavelli died in exile.
威廉·特威德  19世紀紐約州議員
因貪腐入獄  供出同伙后  州政府并未履約釋放他
特威德和州長做了個交易
Boss Tweed made a deal with the governor,
最終卻并未獲釋
but in the end, was never released.
你在哪  簡
Where are you, Jane?
而尼克松被自己的過去困住
And Nixon was a prisoner of his past
到死都沒解脫
till the day he died.
這些人都不知道什么時候該抽身
All men who had no idea how to walk away.
他的尸體還在我手上
I am still in possession of his body,
有必要的話我會用的
and I'll use it, if I have to.
天啊
Oh, God.
不管你聽說了什么
No matter what you hear,
我是想幫你的
I was trying to help you.
簡
Jane.
-就在后面  -你做的很好
- It's around the back. - You did good.
到底是什么
What is it?
她手上到底有什么
What does she have?
你沒必要操心這些事
You don't have to concern yourself with that.
我不是把她給你了嗎
I delivered her, didn't I?
不管簡寧·斯克斯基有什么料都見不到天日了
Whatever Janine Skorsky has will never see the light of day.
她無權公布這些事
She has no right to it.
至于她的消息源  如果知道自己
And her source will be singing a different tune
要蹲多少年牢  一定會改口的
when he sees the jail time he's looking at.
聽聽你這腔調  格雷森先生
Listen to you, Mr. Grayson.
順便一問  你現在是什么頭銜
By the way, what's your title?
我是謝潑德自由基金會
Vice president of research and outreach
研發與推廣副總裁
for the Shepherd Freedom Foundation.
你就像海星  賽斯
You're like a starfish, Seth.
斷了腿總會長回來
Your legs grow back.
這是她的文章
Here's her article.
-郵件呢  -里面有復本
- And the emails? - There's a copy attached.
賽斯在路上了
Seth's on his way.
簡寧說感謝你提前報信
And Janine says thank you for the head's up.
他會帶著大部隊去的
He'll bring the cavalry.
這種困難簡寧應付得了
Calamity Janine can handle herself.
我的狗呢
My dog?
那好了
All right, then.
你到底殺沒殺瑞秋
Did you kill Rachel?
我需要聽你親口說
I need to hear you say it.
你自己也需要說
You need it for yourself.
是我殺的
I did.
但你找不到她的
But you won't find her.
沒人能找得到
No one will.
自首吧
Turn yourself in.
我跟你一起去
Take me.
然后把你埋她的方向指給我
Point me in the direction where you left her.
還有人關心過她呢
There are people who cared for her.
我也關心過她
I cared for her.
佐伊是弗蘭西斯殺的嗎
Did Francis kill Zoe?
告訴我是不是弗蘭西斯殺了佐伊
Tell me if Francis killed Zoe.
現在還是私下說嗎
Is this still off the record?
你知道真相就滿足了嗎
Will it be enough for you to know the truth?
因為你永遠無法證明
Because you're never gonna be able to prove it.
湯姆  你必須滿足  不然我立馬就走
Tom, it has to be enough, or I walk away.
-不  必須有人負責  -天啊  他都死了
- No. Someone has to answer... - Jesus Christ, he's dead.
但是她
But her...
你自己也說過  她和他一樣有罪
You said it yourself, she's as guilty as he is.
要我說甚至她罪更重
I'm saying, maybe more.
也許他這么做都是為了她
Maybe he did it all for her.
你知道什么
What d'you got?
我們達成協議了嗎
Do we have an agreement?
我告訴你真相  你別把他牽涉進來
I give you the truth, and you leave him out of it.
我做不到
I can't do that.
這個世界本就不公平  湯姆
It's not a just world, Tom.
但有時你會有機會讓有罪之人受到懲罰
But sometimes you have the chance to make the right person pay,
哪怕罪名對不上
even if it's for the wrong crime.
難道你還不滿足嗎
Is that enough for you?
因為如果是這樣  那我尊重你的想法
Because if it's not, I respect you,
但我們就此別過
and we can say goodbye.
-不行  道格  我無法滿足  -湯姆
- No, Doug. It's not enough for me. - Tom.
-而且我也絕不同意  -湯姆
- And I do not agree! - Tom.
我永遠不會告訴你
I am never going to tell you
就是弗蘭西斯殺了這三個人
that Francis killed the three of them,
佐伊  羅素
Zoe, Russo
還有莉安
and LeAnn.
但你已經知道真相了
But you already know the truth.
是
Yes.
我確實知道
Yes, I do.
開始記錄
On the record.
從現在開始
From here.
她做了什么
What did she do?
斯克斯基女士
Ms. Skorsky.
聯邦檢察官網絡專案組的人很快就到了
Members of the US Attorney Cyber Task Force are on their way.
我這是在給你機會
I'm giving you a chance.
那我也給你個機會公開回應下吧
And I'm giving you a chance to go on the record.
任何阿卡斯精煉廠或謝潑德無限責任公司旗下
Emails or any correspondence written while at Arcas Refinery
子公司所發出的電郵或其他通信
or any subsidiary of Shepherd Unlimited
均為比爾和安奈特·謝潑德的專有財產
are the sole property of Bill and Annette Shepherd.
那么比爾和安奈特·謝潑德是否知曉
Were Bill and Annette Shepherd aware of the possibility
阿卡斯廠的工人存在死亡的可能
that workers might die at the Arcas plant?
別拿這玩意指著我
Get that outta my face.
我們知道雷·麥耶斯給你發了什么
We know what Ray Meyers sent you.
你有沒有利用阿卡斯泄漏事件
Did you use the Arcas accident
慫恿貝爾波特居民注冊一款應用
to get the citizens of Bellport to sign up for this app?
你協助謝潑德自由基金
An app that you helped develop
開發出來的應用
for the Shepherd Freedom Foundation?
斯克斯基女士
Ms. Skorsky,
他們會沒收你的電腦和其他設備的
they're about to confiscate your computer and any devices.
你現在就可以拿走
You can take it right now.
你什么都不會找到的
You're not gonna find anything here.
我知道你要來  格雷森先生
I knew you were coming, Mr. Grayson.
道格
Doug.
我可以去見總統了
I'm ready to see the President.
按說一個人應該始終如一
You expect a person to be true to his character.
你是那么小心謹慎
You're so careful.
那么擅長清理自己留下的亂子
You're so good about cleaning up after yourself.
為什么沒有處理掉他呢
Why didn't you just get rid of him?
弗蘭西斯另有想法
Well, Francis wanted it otherwise.
我真希望你的答案能讓我意外
I was so hoping you'd surprise me.
你打算怎么做  馬克
What are you gonna do, Mark?
難道你要拉出尸體
You gonna pull out the body,
放到墓碑上展示嗎
drape it over the tombstone?
胡蔓藤可是俄羅斯情報部門常用的毒藥
Gelsemium is known to be used by Russian intelligence.
我要你離開我家
I want you out of my house.
但據我所知  你本來就是一個殺人犯
But from what I understand, you're pretty much a murderer anyway.
你一般不犯錯誤  是不是
You don't normally make mistakes, do you?
但只要犯錯
But when you do,
就犯個大錯
they are something.
難道你內心里就沒希望
Was there some hope in you that
那個迷茫的姑娘會自我了結嗎
the troubled young woman would do herself in?
這樣科爾議員就能解脫了
That Congressman Cole would be relieved somehow.
我要求你立即離開我家  克萊爾
I'd like you to get out of my house, Claire.
你必須要井井有條  毫不留情
It's important to be organized and ruthless.
我一直說事物要分成三種
Three piles, I always say.
你想留著的
The stuff you wanna keep.
先存起來以備后用的
The stuff you might need later that you put in storage.
以及那些必須毀掉的
And the stuff you have to destroy.
-簡  是我  -太對不起了
- Jane, it's me. - I'm so sorry.
我不介意你告訴她了
I don't care that you told her.
你聽見了嗎  我真的不在乎
You hear me? I don't care.
我的偏頭痛
I have the worst migraine
簡直要疼死了
of my life.
簡
Jane.
簡  你還好嗎
Jane, are you okay?
你還好嗎
Are you okay?
簡
Jane.
我差點忘了  還有第四種呢
I almost forgot. There's always a fourth pile.
那些你不知道該怎么處理的
The stuff you don't know what to do with.
您要喝點水嗎
Can I get you some water?
或者別的什么更烈的
Something stronger, maybe?
不了  謝謝  你自己隨意
No, thank you. But don't let me stop you.
我每年的勞工節都要禁一個月的酒
I take a month off drinking, come every Labor Day.
算是某種校歷儀式吧
Kind of an academic calendar ritual
向自己證明我并不酗酒
to prove to myself I'm not actually an alcoholic.
其實我也在節制
I'm actually abstaining myself, at the moment.
是為了
For pursuit of...
看得更清楚吧
clarity, I guess.
想坐坐嗎
Would you like to sit down?
好的
Sure.
他瘋了
He's crazy.
這是有醫生證明的  你知道吧
Certifiable. You know that, right?
道格僅僅一個半月之前
Doug got out of a psychiatric facility
才從精神病院出來
all of a month and a half ago.
無論他多么努力地想復活自己的政治生涯
And no matter how hard he tries to revive his political career
想重新下場
or get back in the game...
他都是個腦筋錯亂的騙子
He's a delusional liar.
而且實話告訴你
And to tell you the truth,
沒準他和弗蘭西斯更般配呢
maybe he was a better wife to Francis.
所以他根本無法清楚地認知事物
Which is why he was never able to see things clearly.
他到底跟你說什么了  湯姆
I mean, what did he tell you, Tom?
你覺得他告訴我什么你不想讓我知道的事了
What do you think he told me that you don't want me to know?
天啊  他肯定跟你說了很多瘋狂臆想
Boy. The fantasies he must have reported to you.
你不得不可憐他
You need to pity him.
真的  我就可憐他
You really do. I do.
總統女士  您這樣擅自闖入
Madam President, this type of intrusion
-公民的私人住所  -聽著  我無法否認
- into a civilian's home... - Listen, there's no denying
弗蘭西斯是個不擇手段的人  做了
that Francis was a desperate man who did,
沒錯  做了許多不擇手段的事
yes, a lot of desperate things.
我不知道  也許到了最后
And I don't know. Maybe towards the end,
他都有點精神錯亂了
he was slightly deranged.
但不管他做了什么  都是他自己做的
But whatever he did, he did alone.
我都沒有參與
I was not complicit.
而且你  還記得最后一次
And do you... Do you remember the last interview
采訪我丈夫的時候嗎
you did with my husband?
在談話的最后  他問你
And the conversation ended where he asked you
你信不信他的話
if you'd believed what he'd told you.
你還記得你怎么回答的嗎
Do you remember how you responded, Tom?
我記得
I do.
我說  一點都不信
I said, "Not for a second."
總統女士
Madam President,
關于你是否是共犯的問題
when it comes to your complicity,
我想我們最好還是在正式場合談一談
I think it's best if we meet under more formal circumstances.
我會給你的新聞辦公室發一份問題清單
I'll be sending over a list of questions to your press office.
你可以通過書信或電郵來回答
You can answer them by mail, email.
如果你愿意的話  當面錄音采訪也行
Or if you prefer, face-to-face and on the record.
她給你掃房子掃了多少年
How many years did she clean up after you?
我的母親  你的管家
My mother, the housekeeper.
從我看見你的那一刻  鄧肯
From the second I saw you, Duncan.
你那漂亮的  皺成一團的小臉
Your beautiful little scrunched up face.
跟小老頭一樣
Like an old man.
那一刻我就知道了
I just knew. It was instant.
我們是一家人
We just belonged,
是一家人  真的
we belonged, we did.
那你為什么沒有合法收養我
Why didn't you legally adopt me?
我想大概是因為沒必要吧
I guess, because I didn't have to.
我父親呢
And my father?
是不是...
Was it...
不是不是
Oh, no, no, no.
一夜情而已
A one night stand.
她
She...
她說她沒記住他的名字
said she didn't remember his name.
我去看她了
I went to see her.
我的生母
My birth mother.
她的住處離這里不到半小時的車程
She lives not more than half an hour from here.
這你知道嗎
Did you know that?
你和她說話了嗎
Did you talk to her?
我沒敢
Couldn't.
我不能那么對她
I couldn't do that to her.
我只是
I just...
我只是遠遠看著她
I just watched her.
她怎么能把我...
How could she let...
我知道我能照顧好你
I knew I could take care of you.
我也知道她照顧不好你
I knew she couldn't.
就算你現在不想
If not now,
我也希望你能原諒我
I hope you can forgive me.
你還好嗎  鄧肯
You okay, Duncan?
幫我說說  比爾
Help me, Bill.
你的親生父母是誰  從哪來的
Who your real parents were, where they came from...
我根本就不在乎
I never cared about any of that.
因為
Because...
你知道因為什么
Well, you know why.
那就說啊
Say it.
他到底是什么人  比爾
Who he is, Bill.
我受夠了
I don't need this.
你不要走
Stay where you are.
-不  -鄧肯
- No. - Duncan,
如果你和我還想做一家人
if you and I are to have any chance,
那你就不要走
you need to stay right here.
比爾  快說啊
Bill, say it.
他對你  對我  到底是什么人
Who he is to you. To me.
親愛的
Honey...
他到底是什么人  快說啊你
Who is he, goddamn it?
他不是咱家的人
He's not one of us.
你個孬種
You're a coward.
讓克萊爾·黑爾替你說出來
Letting Claire Hale say it for you.
我希望你快死
Well, I hope you die.
我們走  走吧
Let's go. Now!
電郵鏈接中的會議記錄清楚地表明
The email links to corporate minutes that clearly indicate
公司提前知道
a foreknowledge of hazard
有發生危及生命安全的災難的可能性
that resulted in catastrophic harm and loss of life.
而列席會議并且同意公司政策的
In attendance and party to consent of the corporate policy
正是公司總裁威廉·謝潑德
was the entity's chief executive officer William Shepherd.
阿卡斯精煉廠負有責任
Arcas Refinery is liable.
謝潑德無限責任公司也一樣
As is Shepherd Unlimited.
公司和比爾·謝潑德本人都可以被指控
The corporation and Bill Shepherd himself can be charged
犯下過失殺人罪
with involuntary manslaughter.
把他打成殺人犯
Expose him as a murderer
順便還能讓他損失幾十億
and cost him billions in the process.
斯克斯基女士會發表嗎
Is Ms. Skorsky publishing?
我親自確保的
I made sure of it.
等你逮捕他  故事就更精彩了
It's a better story once you arrest him.
而這篇文章又可以支持逮捕
And the article will justify the arrest.
我們可以請律師來  至少能拖一拖
We can get some lawyers in here and delay, at the very least.
不
No.
那我們可以安排他們從后門帶你走
Then we can make sure they walk you out the back.
不不不
No, no, no.
不行  我想戴手銬
No, no. I want the cuffs.
總統這次太過分了
President's gone too far this time.
我想讓全世界都看到
I want the whole world to see.
我妹妹呢
And my sister?
你可以在任何地方交給我  為什么在這里
You could've handed me this anywhere, why here?
似乎這里更合適
Seemed appropriate.
你可不是那種懷舊的人  道格
You never struck me as nostalgic, Doug.
難道你還對弗蘭西斯的死后赦免
Could this be about the posthumous pardoning
還有癡心妄想嗎
you've been imagining for Francis?
你不屬于這里
You don't belong here.
我有時候真擔心你胡思亂想
I sometimes worry about your imagination.
你這奴隸一般的忠誠
Your slavish devotion.
你無法去想他之外的事
You can't think beyond him. Not really.
你離開白宮的景象  我倒是想象得很清楚
I can imagine you not in the White House quite clearly.
我的天哪
Oh, my goodness.
你要總是說這樣的話
You keep saying things like that,
我可能就不能放你走了
I might not be able to let you leave.
你怎么處理了
What did you do with it?
他的遺囑
The will.
你燒掉了嗎
Did you burn it?
他把一切都留給我了
He left me everything.
你知道  我也知道
You know it, and I know it.
不好意思
Excuse me.
最近我困得越來越早了
I get sleepy so early these days.
我不會再聽從誰的命令了  道格
I'm not going to be told what to do anymore, Doug.
無論是你  或是別人
Not by you or anyone or any man,
永遠  永遠不會了
ever, ever again.
-給  湯姆  -多謝了  丹
- Here, Tom. - Thanks, Dan.
-不客氣  -很快就好
- No problem. - Won't be long.
沒關系
Whatever.
轉身
Turn.
坐下  坐下
Sit, sit.
好孩子  聽著
Good boy, listen.
-趴下  趴到柜臺下面  -好好
- Get down, below the counter. - Okay, okay.
我怎么說你就怎么做  好嗎
You do exactly like I told you before, okay?
記住  這是在玩呢  記住了
Remember, it's all about having fun, remember?
你一定要乖  沒事的
You be a good boy. It's gonna be all right.
好好玩  好嗎  好
Just have fun, okay? Okay.
剛剛收到的消息
And in breaking news just in,
我們沉痛地宣布《華盛頓先驅報》
we are sad to report that one of the Washington Herald's
最優秀的記者和主編  湯姆·哈默施密特
most accomplished journalists and editors Tom Hammerschmidt
在一次搶劫中不幸中槍  當場身亡
was pronounced dead at the scene of a robbery gone terribly wrong.
白宮很快發表了聲明
The White House was quick to comment,
說就在幾小時前
as the President had sat down
總統曾與這位獲獎記者
with the award-winning Hammerschmidt
進行過面對面的談話
for an interview only hours before.
除表達哀悼之外
Along with her condolences,
總統也借此機會呼吁施行更嚴格的槍支管制
the President used the opportunity to call for greater gun control,
尤其在市中心區
particularly in our inner cities.
該死
Fuck!
他給你的最后一樣東西
The last thing he gave you.
如果你不告訴我是什么意思的話
If you don't tell me what it means...
我倒希望你能告訴我是什么意思  克萊爾
I was kind of hoping you could tell me, Claire.
道格  湯姆·哈默施密特死了
Doug, Tom Hammerschmidt is dead.
還有凱茜  簡
Cathy, Jane.
比爾·謝潑德也要去蹲監獄了
Bill Shepherd is going to prison.
馬克已經四面楚歌
Mark has no one to turn to.
只有你和我了
It's just you and me.
失陪一下
Gimme a moment, please.
你得知道
Please know.
讓這三個可憐人的靈魂
The thought of accelerating the exit
提前從人間消失的決定
of three poor souls from this earth
非常痛苦
is beyond painful.
抱歉了
Sorry about that.
沒關系
Not at all.
我并不擔心你  道格
I'm not worried about you anymore, Doug.
你不會做任何傷害弗蘭西斯的事  你做不到
You wouldn't do anything to hurt Francis. You're not capable.
而且問題在于
And see, the thing is...
不管弗蘭西斯給你留下了什么  都不屬于你
whatever Francis left you, it doesn't actually belong to you.
我們結婚時  把個人和共有財產安排得很清楚
We entered our marriage with a his, hers and ours agreement.
你的財產自己留著  任意處置
You keep and do whatever you want with yours,
而我的也歸我隨意使用
I keep and do whatever I want with mine.
你也想象得到  是我父母堅持的
My daddy and mother insisted, as you can imagine.
不過這個婚前協議  有一個條款
But the prenup we had, had a clause.
如果我們有了后代
If ever we have descendants together
而其中一方先于對方離世
and one of us is first to die,
我們同意將所有權利傳給后代
we agree to waive our rights to everything passed on.
這也就意味著
By which I mean,
弗蘭西斯所有的財產
all of Francis's assets
都屬于他的后代
are entitled to his heir.
如果他有一個的話
If he should have one.
上帝保佑  弗蘭西斯和我有孩子了
Francis and I have been blessed.
盡管同性戀婚姻合法化等熱點議題在美國民眾中越來越受到認同
美國百姓在墮胎合法性問題上的分歧并沒有隨著時間流逝有太多改變
根據蓋洛普調查的歷史數據  認為在懷孕的任何時間點  任何情況下
都可以墮胎的美國人  從1976年的22%緩慢增長到了2018年的29%
而在1976年有21%的美國人認為任何情況下都不能墮胎
這個比例到了2018年維持在20%
在兩種極端觀點變化不大的情況下  在過去四十年中
認為只有在特定情況下才可以墮胎的美國人也始終維持在50%左右
在美國的兩個政治黨派中  共和黨屬于"支持生命派"  整體上反對墮胎
具體到不同的政客
有的極端保守派認為任何情況下墮胎都是對胎兒的謀殺
而一些溫和派的共和黨則同意只有在極端情況下
如被強奸  胎兒診斷出疾病  懷孕威脅母親安全等  才可以進行墮胎
民主黨則整體上是"支持選擇派"
認為女性有權選擇怎樣對待自己的身體
拒絕認為胎兒是一個完整的生命
溫和派的民主黨認為墮胎要慎重  但是最終決定權在于母親
而激進的民主黨則認為
法律和社會在任何情況下都不應阻止懷孕婦女墮胎
在2016年大選中  共和黨候選人特朗普是堅定的反墮胎者
而民主黨候選人希拉里在這一問題上的態度
則從2008年時認為墮胎要慎重  轉為強調墮胎是女性不可剝奪的權力